My name is Godwin Sunday Udoh.
I am a member of Full Gospel Church of God.
This is my daughter, Blessing Godwin Sunday.
This is my first daughter, Mary Godwin Sunday.
This is my third child, Abraham Godwin Sunday.
This is my last born baby, Elijah Godwin Sunday.
I had a very dark incident last year on Wednesday 16 September 2015.
I was coming from church with my family
I was riding a motorised tricycle, known as 'keke maruwa', to ljegun bus stop.
On getting to ljegun bus stop, I saw a group of policemen at the check point.
As soon as I got to ljegun bus stop, one of them brought out a gun to stop me.
I stopped and got out with my wife to ask the policeman what had happened.
One of them said that he didn't want to hear any story from me - he was the one who had a gun.
He said that I should give him 2000 naira
I said we were coming from church; I was not using it as a commercial vehicle.
I said we were going home with my family, my wife and my four children.
and that we were coming from a prayer programme.
That was between the hours of 9 and 10.
I said that I did not have any money with me and that I was going home with my family and my wife.
One of them told us to go but as soon as my wife and I entered the 'keke tricycle'
and I was about to start the engine, I heard two gunshots.
I thought I was the only one the bullet hit.
The bullet cut through my right arm and pierced through my lower jaw.
I came down holding my jaw with blood gushing out
and that was when I heard my children shouting, "Mummy is dying! Mummy is dying!"
As soon as I heard that, I went back, looked inside the 'keke tricycle' and saw
that my wife had dropped the baby.
When I held my wife, I noticed that the bullet had pierced my wife from the right side of her brain
and it had come out through the left side of the brain.
My wife died instantly.
This is my family - my four children and I.
This is when I was in LUTH Hospital where I had undergone an operation after the incident.
This is the female doctor that handled my case.
The man standing here is my brother who has been following me everywhere I go.
Why are you here today? What is the reason that brought you here?
The reason I am here today is because of the gunshot of that day
and my children having had to watch their mother being killed in cold blood.
She died instantly as a result of the bullet.
The shock affected the brain of my first daughter here.
Since that day, she has not been herself.
She had convulsions several times.
I am confused, I need help from Prophet T.B. Joshua and sympathisers.
Please assist me.
My wife is still in the mortuary.
I am still undergoing treatment and I am yet to recover from the injury.
I need financial assistance and healing for my daughter.
You are saying that your daughter, because of the trauma of seeing her mother killed before her,
it has affected her psychologically since then?
Exactly. Since then, she has not been herself and also the rest of them.
My message to my brother, whatever you might have said,
I want to let you know that whatever that will lead to our last day on earth -
whether a plane crash, motor accident, gunshot, kidnapping,
dropped in hot soup, being panned or whatever -
does not testify to our Christian life, but the life we live is the one that matters.
I want you to put everything behind you.
While this was going on, there were a lot of text messages that came in from all over
and more are still coming in.
A gentleman here donated one million naira.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
A lot of other donations - even from overseas countries.
There is a donation of pounds and others.
Once this assistance comes, you will become part of our family and we will become part of your family.
We want you to forget everything, put it behind you.
Godwin Sunday Udoh & Family Share Experience
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So that your dear one can rest in peace.
All this is disturbing the soul.
The soul wants to rest. It doesn't want to hear all this disturbance.
You said that you were coming from church.
Ehe!
That is to tell you that God is aware.
Godwin Sunday Udoh & Family Share Experience
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The ministry here and the partners, apart from other partners donating - we are ready to give 5 million naira.
Godwin Sunday Udoh & Family Share Experience
Like I have said - other partners from all over the world are donating.
As they are donating, we will keep on giving it to you.
This is the reason why they wanted you to come out. They are supporting you.
We are not here to judge. If we judge, who will judge us on the last day.
Your dear one was coming from the place of worship.
Unless you don't believe that your dear one was coming from a living church.
If you know that she was coming from church, what else again.
Whatever happened, God is aware.
Please, put everything behind you.
All the financial support you need, you are part of our family from today.
We are going to add you to the martyr we have all over the world.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We will put your family among the dear ones we have in the past, we will take care of you.
Okay? Put it behind you.
Children, how are you?
Thank you.
TESTIMONY TIME
God bless you. My name is Godwin Sunday Udoh.
I am from Akwa Ibom state, Nigeria
An incident happened to me.
I was the man that the police shot at and killed my wife last year on September 16, 2015.
I was helpless after the incident happened. Nobody could help me.
I had to rush to Prophet T.B. Joshua, crying to him.
As soon as they saw me, they quickly helped me.
They gave me the sum of 5 million naira to establish and treat myself and to take care of my children.
Not only that - other partners from all over the world and from Nigeria as well supported me.
I really appreciate the good works of the man of God towards me and my family.
May the Lord bless him, in Jesus' name.
I was adviced by the man of God to go and bury my wife and forget about the past and the police.
I had to obey.
I just came back from burying my wife and this is the programme of the burial.
My children are now in school.
May the Lord's name be glorified, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Let's put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Mr Godwin Sunday Udoh & Children Sharing Life Experience
We thank God Almighty for what He has done in your life.
As you rightly said, after the incidence happened,
you moved from one place to another - all to no avail - in search of solution and help,
until you found your way to The SCOAN.
After narrating your ordeal, the man of God was touched with the Lord's compassion
and he summoned Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world
and also gave you the sum of 5 million naira to support you and the entire family
and also to assist in your wife's burial.
You are here to tell us that you have completed the burial activities,
you have established yourself and your children are back to school.
Is that what you are trying to say?
Yes.
Let's put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Mr Godwin Sunday Udoh & Children Sharing Life Experience
Without taking much of your time, could you just give a word of advice to all that are listening to you,
concerning the goodness of the Lord in your life.
My advice to the world today is that:
No matter the situation you are experiencing, put your trust and faith in the Lord,
believing that God will surely meet you at the point of your needs, in the mighty name of Jesus.
May the Lord bless the man of God and continue to take him higher and higher
and also promote this ministry, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
To God be the glory!
Before you go finally, we also want to update the viewers concerning your daughter,
who developed facial palsy as a result of witnessing the horrible incident of the mother's death.
What do you have to say about your daughter's condition right now?
God has taken control.
God has done marvellously well by healing her.
After ministering the morning water that was given to me by the Prophet,
my daughter recovered and she was healed.
Let's clap for wonderful Jesus Christ for that!